<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earlytime</title>
    <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Earlytime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://afaf28.github.io/site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/articles/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/blog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ChatBot Platform</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/chatbot_platform_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/chatbot_platform_info/</guid>
      <description>Earlytime creates an autonomus knowledge base powered by Artificial Intelligence. The knowledge base is easy to access, always up to date and includes on the field know-how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Company’s DNA</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/dna_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/dna_info/</guid>
      <description>We are working with the Canopé network to propose a learning platform and collaborate with the National Education. This is our cause and our DNA. The team spends 20% of the time on this project, and soon, a usable prototype will be open to the public.
For more information please contact us !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact us for Demo</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/contactdemo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/contactdemo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make sure your next product or service launch drives growth</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/second_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/second_post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our conviction is that Knowledge increases by sharing but not by saving</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/about/</guid>
      <description>EarlyTime creates artificial intelligence to assist employees in their daily tasks and accelerate the knowledge and skill sharing. We dematerialize your company, managers, experts and make them available instantly and simultaneously to users. Also, we mobilize all human resources and virtual assistants to provide a solution for each employee’s question.
EarlyTime offers a unique feature:
 e-DZO : a personal coach for each employee. It manages access to knowledge and offers an adaptive training path customized to everyone’s personal need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our conviction is that Knowledge increases by sharing but not by saving</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/first_post/</guid>
      <description>EarlyTime creates artificial intelligence to assist employees in corporations in their daily tasks and accelerate the knowledge and skill sharing. We dematerialize your company, managers, experts and make them available instantly and simultaneously to users. Also, we mobilize all human resources and virtual assistants to provide a solution for each employee’s question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our conviction is that Knowledge increases by sharing but not by saving</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/third_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/third_post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solutions</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/solutions/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. Our solutions Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/team/</guid>
      <description>A solid, complementary, experienced team enjoying this fabulous journey of transforming the knowledge organization in corporations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e-DZO</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/edzo_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/edzo_info/</guid>
      <description>e-Dzo is a virtual coach able to collect information through a simple dialogue, respond to questions, find solutions to regularly encountered problems, make recommendations, train individuals.
e-Dzo is smart, intuitive and adapts to users. He integrates each team to capture, organise, store, spread and make the team’s knowledge widely available in your company. e-Dzo is an avatar of teams’ expertise.
He is powered by artificial intelligence, and becomes the team’s memory holder, responsible for mastering the team’s know-how and expertise to provide it easily and instantaneously to any employee who may need it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e-DZO’s team</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/edzo_team_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/edzo_team_info/</guid>
      <description>«Tell me and I forget. Teach me and I remember. Involve me and I learn.» Benjamin Franklin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e-Dzo Users</title>
      <link>https://afaf28.github.io/site/edzo_users_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://afaf28.github.io/site/edzo_users_info/</guid>
      <description>e-dzo provides an adaptative learning path to improve your skills and help you increase clients’ satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>